

Kesya WijayaSoftware Developer Tangerang, Indonesia

+6281904363902

github.com/karacelly

□ aracellykesya@gmail.com

∂ https://kesyawijaya.com

Enthusiastic Computer Science graduate with a keen interest in software engineering. I bring three years of experience as a Software Laboratory Assistant and one year as an Operation and System Development Staff at Binus University. Actively pursuing personal and professional growth, I am engaged in freelance projects to stay updated with industry trends. Eager to apply my skills and knowledge in a challenging software engineering role.

Work Experience

Application Developer

Feb 2023 - Feb 2024

Bina Nusantara University

- Designed and implemented a robust and user-friendly interface for tracking staff attendance utilizing face recognition, enhancing efficiency and accuracy in monitoring student presence.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to conceptualize, design, and develop a web-based course pricing model.

Operations and System Development Staff

Aug 2022 - Feb 2024

Bina Nusantara University

- Providing technical support in network, system and infrastructure for activities that were held in or by Software Laboratory.
- Installation and maintenance of servers and workstations. Hardware upgrade for servers and workstations.

Laboratory Assistant

Feb 2021 - Feb 2024

Bina Nusantara University

 Tutor and marker for Multimedia Programming Foundation (COMP7094), Database (ISYS6084), Operating System (COMP6153001), Object Oriented Analysis & Design (COMP6115001), Framework Layer Architecture (COMP6122001), Data Structures (COMP6048001), Human & Computer Interaction (COMP6800001), Computer Vision (COMP7116001), and Scientifc Computing (MATH6183001)

Website Developer Aug 2023 - Nov 2023

Universitas Katolik Parahyangan

- Design and develop a visually stunning and user-friendly website for SAA Awards XLI, an annual architecture competition hosted by Parahyangan Catholic University and Indonesian Institute of Architects.
- Maintain the website throughout the duration of SAA Awards XLI, ensuring its smooth operation, security, and optimal performance.
- Provide technical support and troubleshooting in case of any issues or updates required during the event.

Tokopedia Devcamp Class of 2022

Oct 2022

Tokopedia

- Selected as one of participants out of 4900+ applicants to join 7-day exclusive bootcamp training to learn how to use technology especially in Backend curriculum.
- Building impactful products through the virtual hackathons, and extend network to fellow tech enthusiasts.

Educational Background

Bina Nusantara University

2020 - 2024

Sarjana Komputer - S. Kom Current GPA: 3.93

Achievements

Scholarship Mentor

Oct 2021 - Jan 2023

Received 16 credits scholarship for every semester.

Top 40 INC 2021 Oct 2021

Managed to get 39th place out of 600+ teams participated in INC 2021.